gplzone.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy - GPLZONE

Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to keep your personal information confidential and understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations. A recent law change requires us (along with banks, brokerage houses, and other financial institutions) to disclose our Privacy Policy to you – which we are more than happy to do. We hope that by taking a few minutes to read it, you will have a better understanding of what we do with the information you provide us and how we keep it private and secure.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at ikaku002@gmail.com.

At woocrack.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by us and how it is used.

We may collect the following information:

  * your name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer

What we do with the information we gather  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

Controlling your personal information

  * You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
  * a) whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purpose
  * b) if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at ikaku002@gmail.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to  ikaku002@gmail.com. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
